<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 15:13:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Project Management concepts on a Web development enviroment</title>
      <link>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/pmweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 15:13:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/pmweb/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Nowadays, is really popular to use websites to promote your business. Any company who is starting your business wants to have your website, so the customers will have a glimpse of the experience or knowlegde of the place, and also this will make their decision easier if they want to go or hire that service. As a result of this, there is a high demand of websites to the web agencies, where they need to develop something pleasant, with great UI experience and as fast as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience on learning Web and Mobile languages</title>
      <link>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/code_experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 16:06:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/code_experience/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This posting is to show my experience on learning Web and Mobile languages nowadays. Even though I have a Bachelor of Computer Science, technology changes so fast that is extremely hard to keep updated if you are not working in the industry. However, it was faster to learn with the background I have than if I was totally new to software development.
I graduated in 2008 in Brazil in a public University, similar to UBC, after 4 years in a Computer Science program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to network on IT industry after you graduate</title>
      <link>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 12:28:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/networking/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Nowadays, it is getting hard to find a job in the IT Industry. There are a bunch of job postings, which requires a lot of experience on a few technologies. This can scare people, who recently graduated from University, College and other Tech Courses. Moreover, just having the tech skills it is not enough to be employed. The companies are requiring people to have strong soft skills, willing to work in teams, learn about the company&amp;rsquo;s business, to be a good presenter, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby on Rails Installation</title>
      <link>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/ruby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 16:36:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daniel-fonseca.com/posts/ruby/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Ruby on Rails is being used for some of most of relevant companies in the world, such as Git Hub, AirBnb, Groupon, Hulu, etc. In addition, there is a high demand for Ruby on Rails on the labor market for web back-ending development. However, there are some languages in the market where you must take into account, before considering to use Ruby in your project.
Here are some Advantages and Disadvantages of developing on Ruby on Rails :</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>